Michelle Prather Multimedia Designer

Objective

My passions are web design, branding & typography. I have experience in art direction, graphic design, video editing, motion graphics & UI/UX design. I graduated from The Art Institute of California–Orange County in December 2014 and the recipient of the Best in Show Award at the September 2014 Graduate Portfolio Show. My hobbies include painting, photography & illustration. During my education, I have worked on a variety of projects that engages visual communication. I am looking forward to working as a creative professional and picking up new skills and techniques to add to my creative repertoire.

My Specialties

Web Design Graphic Design Art Direction UX Design

Branding Typography HTML/CSS Wordpress

Javascript/jQuery PHP/MvSQL

Education

2011-2014

BA in Web Design and Interactive Media

The Art Institute of California—Orange County Recieved the Dean's Honor Roll 2011 - 2014 and Best in Show at the September 2014 Graduate Portfolio Show.

Technical Skills

Adobe
Photoshop
Illustrator
Dreamweaver
InDesign
After Effects
Premiere Pro
Flash
Unity 3D

My Portfolio



www.michelle-prather.com

Bē

www.behance.net/michelleeprather

Get in touch

Represented by The Greative Group (310)209-6840

Experience

2014 - 2015

Insteo (part-time)

www.insteo.com

Front-end design and development. Wordpress development with social media integration. Development of digital menu-boards.

2014 - 2015

LEARN (freelance)

www.learnla.org

Custom Wordpress site. Front-end design and development with back-end customizations. User-engagement design.

2014 - 2015

Help for Brain Injured Children (freelance)

www.hbic.org

Custom Wordpress site with social media integration. Custom admin panel for Board Members.

2013 - 2014

Food Cartel (internship)

www.food-cartel.com

Responsible for front-end design, creation of visual assets, and creating a positive user experience.

2011 - present

Baddeley's Pourhouse (freelance)

www.baddeleyspourhouse.com

Front-end design and development, integration of social media API's and coordinating marketing materials for social media.